Now, we'll learn a very important concept called regularization.
现在我们将要学习一个非常重要的概念 叫做正则化
This is a very useful technique to improve our models and make sure they don't overfit.
这是改善我们模型 确保不会过度拟合的有效技巧
And notice that this concept works for regression and for classification.
注意这个概念可以用于回归和分类
We'll actually explain it using a classification problem but as you can see,
我们实际上可以利用分类问题对它进行解释 但是正如你看到的
all the arguments here work just as well with regression algorithms.
所有参数值都与回归算法一样发挥作用
So, let's look at some data.
那么我们来看一下这些数据
And here's the data,
这是一些数据
and let's make two copies of it.
并且拷贝了一份这些数据
And let's look at two models that classify this data.
我们看一下分类数据的两个模型
The first one is a line,
第一个是一条直线
and the second one is a higher degree polynomial.
第二个是高次多项式
So, the question is, which one is better?
那么问题是 哪个更好呢？
Well, they both have their pros and cons, right?
两种方法是不是各有利弊？
The one on the left makes a couple of mistakes, as you can see,
左侧这个存在各种错误
there's a red point and the blue in the wrong side,
可以看到 有一个红点和蓝点都在错误位置
but it's much simpler.
但是这种方法更加简单
And the one on the right makes zero mistakes,
右侧这个没有任何错误
but it's actually a bit more complicated.
但实际上有点更加复杂
So, let's say we want the one on the left,
那么如果我们想要左侧这个
because the one on the right overfits,
因为右侧这个过度拟合
and it just doesn't generalize well.
并且不具有较好的通用性
So, the problem is that when we train the model,
所以问题在于当我们训练模型时
the one in the right will appear more likely and the reason is the following.
右侧这个更可能出现 原因如下
Let's say the question is 3X_1 + 4X_2 + 5 = 0, for the line,
例如直线 3X1 + 4X2 + 5 = 0
and equation of polynomial something much more
多元方程式可能更加复杂
complicated with higher degree terms like X_1_squared,
包括高次项 例如
or X_1, X_2, or X_1_cubed et cetera.
X1 的平方或 X1 乘以 X2 或者 X1 的三次方等
But when we're training the model,
但是当我们训练模型时
the model takes an error and minimizes it.
模型得到误差 并进行最小化
So, the one in the left has a small error,
所以左侧这个误差较小
because it makes these two mistakes,
因为只有两个错误
but it's an error nonetheless.
但是只有一个误差
So, this is the error it gets.
这样就可以求出误差
The one on the right has a much smaller error because it doesn't misclassify any point.
因为右侧这个分类没有错误 所以误差更小
So, any model in its right mind would pick the one on the right.
那么任何正确的模型都会拾取右侧的一个
So, how do we do to pick the one in the left?
那么我们如何拾取左侧的呢？
Well, here's an idea,
答案是这样的
if we look at this polynomial,
如果我们观察这个多项式
it's much simpler than the one in the right, and in particular,
这个要比右侧的更加简单
the coefficients are small, that three, four, five,
系数更小 如 3 4 5
whereas if I look at this one.
而如果我们看这个
These numbers are much bigger.
这些数字更大一些
So, it's a lot more of them.
所以可能还会更多
So, if we find a way to increment the error by some function of these numbers,
如果我们通过这些数字的函数找到增加误差的方法
that would be very helpful.
那将会非常有帮助
So, let's do that,
我们来做一下
and I'll show you the detail later,
随后我会向你展示细节
but the idea is that we take
这种想法是我们求出
these three and four and notice we're forgetting about the constant term,
这里的 3 和 4 注意我们这里忽略了常数项
there's a reason for that.
其中一个原因
But if we take this three and four and add them to the error,
但是如果我们这里求出 3 和 4 并加到误差中
we get a slightly bigger error.
我们得到稍大一些的误差
But what if we take this two two four minus three six four,
但是如果我们得到 2 2 4 -3 6 4
and add them to the error, and now we get a huge error.
并加到误差中 会得到很大的误差
And now we can see that the model on the left is better,
现在我们看到左侧模型更好一些
because it has a smaller error.
因为它的误差更小
So, in summary what we did is,
所以 总之我们要做的是
we took the complexity of the model into account when we calculated the error,
在计算误差时考虑模型的复杂性
and then that way a simpler model has an edge over a complicated model.
简单的模型比复杂的模型更胜一筹
And simpler models tend to generalize better.
简单的模型更具有通用性
So, that's what we want.
那是我们想要的
But let me be more detailed on how to
但是让我更详细地讲解下
take those green coefficients and turn them into part of the error.
如何利用这些绿色的系数 把它们转化为误差的一部分
There's a method called L1 regularization, and it's very simple.
这种方法叫做 L1 正则化 非常简单
This is a complicated polynomial.
这是个复杂的多项式
And what it does is it takes the coefficients and just adds the absolute values.
它的作用在于可以得出系数 并且把它们的绝对值加起来
So, as you can see there is two minus two minus four etc.
所以可以看到 这是 2 -2 -4 等
it just takes the absolute value of those and adds them to 21.
得到这些数字的绝对值 加起来后是 21
And in this case, you can see that we're taking
在这个例子中 可以看到我们得到
the absolute values of three and four, and we get seven.
3 和 4 的绝对值 得到 7
So, seven is much less than 21.
那么 7 远远小于 21
So, that's why the complicated model gives you a much higher error.
所以这就是为什么复杂的模型得出较大的误差
That's L1 regularization and L1 is attached to the absolute value.
这就是 L1 正则化 它与绝对值相关
L2 regularization is very similar.
L2 正则化是类似的
And what we do here is,
我们这里要做的
instead of taking the absolute value,
不是得到绝对值
we just add the squares of the coefficients.
而是把系数的平方加起来
So, we get 2_squared plus -2_squared plus -4_squared etc, we get 85.
所以我们得到 2 的平方加 -2 的平方加上 -4 的平方等等 最后得到 85
And for the linear case,
在直线的这个例子中
we just get 3_squared plus 4_squared which is 25, which is much smaller.
我们得到 3 的平方加 4 的平方等于25 这个值更小
So again we can see that the complex model gets
所以可以再次看到 复杂的模型
punished a lot more than the simple model.
比简单的模型受到更多惩罚
But now, the question is how do we tune these parameters,
但是现在问题是我们如何调优这些参数
because maybe we want a bit of the more complicated model etc.
因为我们想用更复杂一点的模型
So, we have this parameter called lambda,
所以我们这个参数称为 λ
and what lambda does is it multiplies into the complexity error,
λ 的用途是可以乘以复杂误差
multiplies into that green error to make it bigger or smaller.
乘以那个绿色的误差可以变大或变小
So, let's say we have a small 位.
所以如果有个小的 λ
We take the green error and multiply it by a small 位,
我们得到绿色的误差 把它乘以 λ
so we get something very small.
我们就会得到很小的结果
So, the model in the right still wins because the error is smaller,
所以因为误差更小 所以右侧还是胜出
and we have some complexity error but it's much smaller.
我们得到某个复杂误差 但是这个误差更小
Now, if we take a large 位 then we're multiplying the green error by a lot,
现在如果我们有个大的 λ 乘以绿色的误差
and now we can see that the simpler model
这是可以看到简单的模型
is much better because it gives us a smaller error.
更好 因为它的误差更小
So in summary, this is what happens if we have a large lambda,
所以总体说来 如果我们有个大的 λ
then we're punishing complexity by a lot,
我们会更多地惩罚复杂性
and we're picking a simpler model.
拾取更加简单的模型
Whereas if we have a small 位 then we're punishing complexity by a small amount,
然而如果我们有个小的 λ 我们会以较小数量惩罚复杂性
so we are okay with having more complex models.
所以我们可以使用更复杂的模型
Now the question is which one to use, L1 or L2?
现在的问题是我们应该使用哪个呢？ L1 还是 L2？
So here's a cheat sheet with some benefits of each L1 and L2.
这里是每个 L1 和 L2 优点的备忘单
So L1 regularization is actually computationally
所以 L1 正则化实际上计算起来
inefficient even though it seems simpler,
效率不高 虽然看起来更简单
because it doesn't have squares.
不包括平方
But actually those absolute values are hard to differentiate.
但是这些绝对值很难求导(求微分)
Whereas in L2 regularization,
但是 L2 正则化中
the squares have a very nice derivative and so
平方是比较不错的导数
that makes things very easy to do computationally.
所以可以计算起来更加容易
The only time L1 regularization is faster than L2 is when the data is sparse.
只有数据稀疏时  L1 正则化会比 L2 正则化更快
So, let's say you have a thousand counts of data,
那么如果说你有 1000 次数据运算
but really only 10 of them are relevant,
实际上只有 10 个具有相关性
and there's a lot of zeroes in between then L1 is better.
其中包括很多 0 那么 L1 正则化更好些
So, as I said, L1 is better for sparse outputs,
所以正如我说过的 L1 正则化适合稀疏输出
and L2 is better for non-sparse outputs.
L2 正则化更适合非稀疏输出
When there's just a lot of column to our zero, L1 is better.
如果很多列包含 0 那么 L1 正则化更好些
But when the data is very equally distributed among columns and the L2 is better.
但是如果数据均匀分布在各列 那么 L2 正则化更好些
And L1 has one huge benefit which is that it gives this feature selection.
L1 正则化最大的好处在于提供特征选择
So, let's say we have again data of a thousand columns,
所以如果我们有 1000 列数据
but really only 10 of them matter,
实际上只有 10 列数据相关
and the rest are just noise.
其他的都是噪音
L1 will notice this and will make those irrelevant columns of data zero.
L1 可以注意到这一点 把不相关的数据转变为 0
L2 on the other hand, will not do this.
而 L2 就无法做到这一点
L2 will just kind of take all the columns and treat them
L2 会对所有列平等对待
equally and give us a combination of all of them as our result.
并且给我们所有数据的总和作为结果
So, that's it.
所以就是这样
That's regularization.
这就是正则化